LUKAS GLODEK

07946 780649

lukas.glodek.dev@gmail.com

Profile

Hardworking and enthusiastic Web Developer from Birmingham, currently living in London. Have working knowledge of HTML, CSS and Java Script. Holds a degree in Nutrition and Dietetics from Birmingham University and is an experienced English Teacher.

Experience

Web Developer, 2022

- Completed a range of projects using HTML, CSS, Word Press and Java Script.
- Work can be viewed at https://lukas-design.netlify.app

English teacher at "English Connection" in Seville, 2019-2022

- Business English classes in a professional office type environment. Groups consisted of 5-10 students. Classes were focused on improving students ability to use English related to renewable energy and general comprehension.
- Football orientated classes at Real Betis Football club. Due to a big number of students (groups and individuals) classes ranged from professional football vernacular to more general approach. During my time at Real Betis I also participated in an English football camp as a football coach to kids age 7-12.
- Teacher at an academy. Preparing kids and teenagers for a Cambridge exam.
 Most experience with B1 and B2, but I also worked with A2.

Personal trainer and football coach, B-active gym, Birmingham, 2017-2019

- one to one personal training sessions with clients from various age groups and backgrounds.
- delivered professional workout and nutrition programmes.
- have build an excellent relationship with all clients and children.

English teacher at "speak up", Gdansk, Poland, 2016-2017

- experience in teaching children, teenagers and adults.
- used to working full-time schedule and preparing and delivering classes to a variety of levels and needs.
- successfully prepared students for the exams.

Personal trainer, Cuesta Sport, Seville, June/July 2016

- one to one personal training sessions with clients from all over Europe.
- developed the ability to communicate with clients with limited Spanish.
- gave English lessons through personal training.

Supervisor at Quest Healthcare Limited, 2013-2016

- managed a small team.
- developed ability to present and to give speeches.
- showed great responsibility and organisation by meeting deadlines.

Education

- Birmingham Metropolitan College, Fitness and Personal Training, (2014-2016)
- Birmingham City University, Human Nutrition and Dietetics, (2010-2013)
- Sutton Coldfield College, Birmingham, IT software development, (2006-2008)

Skills

Languages - Native level of both English and Polish. Basic Spanish.

References

Available on request